{
    "id": "c02f7032a2924d41ae1548efd446ade0",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Maria is a nice girl, …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is she",
                "isn't she",
                "does she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d8035302e69f4cc3ac1e9fbeda7cec90"
        },
        {
            "question": "What year did you ………………. university?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "graduate",
                "graduate from",
                "graduate at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "016b72ed627e42b6939b826a4e887534"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you enjoy ………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "skating",
                "skate",
                "to skate"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b24931bd5577409a809ccde2c9dfb24f"
        },
        {
            "question": "We didn’t have any trouble .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to find the house",
                "finding the house",
                "to finding the house"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "48ea3aa774644951b036d80c3b78048b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… him yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "have met",
                "had met"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8f1e89170cb5461aa940f831686f1214"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you have questions, don’t hesitate .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ask",
                "to ask",
                "to asking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e15012f0aebe47db942e34c85a52f52d"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are always ready to go to ……………….. help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "one another's",
                "each other's",
                "other's"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f8152ff652404c6abd227e12b79295c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the woman ………………… husband was killed by the dacoits.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "who",
                "of whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2b26b081e00e4a7880a182c29c569e9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I could have married her if I …………………. to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wanted",
                "had wanted",
                "want"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f57a011a2fbb4e13988a4ac2cb631910"
        },
        {
            "question": "Yesterday, I …………………. to go out with Peter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am allowed",
                "was allowed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8892bb9c382442298fa100834b3da1f6"
        }
    ]
}